Fine.
I won't tell anyone.
Huh?
In return...
I want you...
to make a contract with me.
A contract?
Yes...
A contract... with me.
Huh. Someone's here!
NAKAMURA
Hey!
- What are you--
- I see.
What is it?
So this is what the hand of a pervert that
fondled Saeki's gym clothes smells like.
I didn't fondle them!
Don't try to hide it.
I'll keep your secret
about the gym clothes,
but in exchange,
you have to reveal everything to me.
That's our contract.
Still, I didn't fondle...
Hey, want a sniff?
- My hands smell nice these days.
- No, I'm good.
- Why not? Take a sniff.
- No...
No thanks. Stop it!
I don't want to!
Come on, sniff it. Sniff it!
- I'll pass!
- Smell that?
Let me go!
We can't let this go!
Who stole them?
We told you we don't know.
Why do you assume one of us guys did it?
Right, Kasuga?
Obviously, it's a guy
that stole Nanako's gym clothes!
Hey, Nakamura.
Where were you
when Nanako's gym clothes went missing?
Wait, Nakamura's a suspect?
You know,
I think I saw her heading back here.
For real?
What?
No, no, no. It's not Nakamura.
Get out of my way, shitty scum.
What?
How dare you...
You did it, didn't you?
- Out of my way.
- That hurt!
Yeah, I'm sure of it now!
You all saw that, right?
That was assault. Assault!
You gotta be kidding me.
See, it was one of the girls after all.
Theft is crazy, though.
- It's a straight-up crime.
- Right?
Hey, are you even awake?
- No.
- Say something.
Think of poor Nanako!
No, you've got it wrong.
- Are you listening?
- No. No.
It's not her!
Uh... No, I mean...
You... You don't have proof or anything.
What?
What is this?
Kasuga, do you have a crush on Nakamura?
- No, that's not--
- Kasuga, no way! Seriously?
- Kasuga.
- No, I don't!
- Man, what kind of taste do you have?
- Stop it! Cut it out.
- Think about it objectively.
- You can tell me anything.
:cue
- Stop it.
- Objectively?
- Cut it out! Sit down.
- What about her do you like?
Nakamura, of all people?
Man, he's something else.
Darn it! How did this happen?
I don't have feelings for Nakamura...
Hey, want a sniff?
My hands smell nice these days.
No, it's not like that!
I...
My Venus is...
Kasuga.
Huh?
What?
Shoot! No way. What?
Who's she talking to? To me? Saeki?
Saeki?
Kasuga...
I can't believe
you'd say something like that.
No! Well, you see... That was...
That was really cool.
What?
What are you grinning about?
Wait, do you have a fever or something?
- I guess not.
- This is adolescence.
Proof that he's growing up healthy.
Mmm...
Your eyes are transparent prisms.
That was really cool.
With ease,
you expel the irredeemable sin within me.
That was really cool.
SAEKI
I will never take these out again.
Thank you, Saeki,
for cleansing me of my sin.
THE FLOWERS OF EVIL
EPISODE 2
Finally,
about Saeki's gym clothes...
We received a report that a suspicious man
was wandering near the school that day.
The police want to ask you some questions,
so we'll have study hall for first period.
Quiet. Keep it down.
Yes, sir.
:cue
Hey, Kasuga.
You seemed really eager
to defend Nakamura yesterday.
I bet you know something
about this suspicious man.
There you go, reading that book again.
As if you understand any of it.
Reporting from the scene of the crime,
we'll now ask Mr. K
about the sighting of a suspicious man.
- Mr. K, Mr. K, Mr. K!
- What is this?
Do you know anything about the man?
What's your relationship to the victim,
Ms. Nanako Saeki?
- Mr. K, Mr. K, Mr. K!
- What is this? Come on, go home!
See ya!
- Mr. K!
- Huh?
When you're done cleaning,
meet me behind the school.
- Hey, Kasuga.
- Huh?
All done cleaning?
- Yeah.
- Thanks as always.
Uh... Need help with that?
What?
Aren't you in a hurry, though?
Uh... No, not at all.
Three crows.
Four crows.
He's late!
By the way,
I forgot to mention this yesterday, but...
What is it?
No way. Does she know?
About the other day...
I'm sorry.
Sorry... For what?
When you bumped into me in the library...
...you didn't do it on purpose,
but I freaked out and ran out of the room.
Sorry about that.
Ah... No, well...
You know,
I was wondering.
What do you do for fun, Kasuga?
Um...
I go to the used bookstore
on the shopping street.
My dad said that they carry rare books
that you wouldn't even find in Tokyo.
Wow! That sounds interesting.
It does?
The used bookstore...
I haven't been there.
I wonder what it's like.
Would... you like to go?
Like, this Sunday?
What?
No, I mean, you don't have to...
We don't have to go together.
- Never mind. Forget it.
- What?
Wait, what was that? Say it again.
Sorry...
Wanna go?
This Sunday?
Really?
:cue
Kasuga!
Hey!
How are you feeling?
You're about to go
on your first date with Saeki.
Are you excited?
What is it?
Why did you drag me in here?
Do you have the thing...
I told you to bring?
COME 30 MIN. EARLY.
BRING SAEKI'S GYM CLOTHES.
I vowed I'd never open this again...
THE FLOWERS OF EVIL
I mean, I did, but...
Okay then, get changed.
Wear her gym clothes underneath
during your date today.
What the...
No, no way. Absolutely not!
Shut up and get changing!
You freaking perverted human.
Why are you making me...
Is this because...
you're jealous?
Jealous?
What are you thinking?
Are there maggots in your brain,
you scrap metal?
You see,
I've made up my mind.
I'm going to strip away
every layer of the skin
you're hiding behind.
What the...
Get out!
Yes, ma'am.
Stand up straight!
I knew you'd look great in gym bloomers.
You soggy rat.
Yeah, you look great in that.
It's a nice shirt.
You... you think so?
- You do!
- Thanks.
Wow.
So there's a used bookstore
down this street?
- What's wrong?
- Huh?
Oh... It's nothing...
It's kind of hot today, isn't it?
Is it?
You could unbutton your shirt.
Well, no, it's not that hot.
What? Well... Okay, then.
:cue
USED BOOKS AND GALLERY - NEKOMACHI-DO
This is amazing.
- Welcome. Hello there.
- Hello.
Wow.
So this is the shop you come to often.
They have Nadja by André Breton!
Wow!
Kasuga, you really love books, don't you?
I do.
Which book is your favorite, Kasuga?
Oh... I wonder if there's a copy...
Let's see...
THE FLOWERS OF EVIL
Ah. Here it is.
This one.
What?
Wow...
It looks kind of scary.
The first time I read this,
my whole world changed.
The words are just mind-blowing.
Really?
Just mind-blowing...
Uh... Hey, I know!
Here.
This is for you.
What?
Please read it.
I swear it'll blow your mind.
What?
I'm so touched. It's The Flowers Of Evil!
You know, I'm always stuck
either practicing piano or studying.
I read books sometimes, but they're always
from the recommended books list...
Kasuga, do you...
What?
Where'd you go?
Kasuga?
Hey, what are you doing?
Stay out of my--
Shh!
Amazing.
I can hear your heart pounding.
You little pervert.
No, that's... It's not--
Kasuga,
you're hiding
behind so many layers of skin.
It's time to peel back a layer.
By the time you go home today,
kiss Saeki.
- Huh?
- Do it.
You're gonna kiss Saeki
while wearing her gym clothes!
Kasuga?
Where are you?
You'd better do it.
'Cause if you don't...
I'll send you to hell.
:cue
- I was so surprised.
- Huh?
You just disappeared!
Oh!
Saeki has an onion
hanging out of her mouth...
Oh... Oh... Look at that...
What?
Hurry up, kiss her,
you absolute pervert.
No, I'm not!
I'm not!
I'm not a pervert!
What?
Saeki,
could I... I mean...
Could you go out with me,
in a purely platonic kind of way?
Kasuga...
No! Never mind!
I take it back! I'm sorry!
I would be...
honored.
What?
What did you say?
I've...
never had anyone
confess their feelings to me.
My whole life,
I've done everything
for my parents' approval.
And now, I...
I don't have a sense of self.
But...
you're not like that, Kasuga.
Kasuga,
you're so devoted to books...
...and having someone like that
tell me that he likes me...
It really...
It makes me so happy.
I'm happy too.
Really happy.
Yeah.
Thank you.
I look forward to
spending more time with you.
Are you alright?
You can't look!
Kasuga?
No, I mean... Sorry!
I remembered I had something to do!
What? Kasuga!
Did she see it?
Did I get away with it?
Damn it, Nakamura!
Nakamura!
That was so mean of you!
Shut it, traitor.
Told you to strip those layers!
I told you to kiss her!
You were turned on by wearing this!
:cue
You're just a disgusting,
freaky little perverted piece of shit!
I...
I've had...
a tingling feeling
for so long now.
It's in my body...
down there...
inside...
It's like it's screaming.
I want this whole world
to turn into a shit bug,
engulfed by my frustration.
I suppose I'm a pervert...
too.
"Too"?
Fine, then. Why don't you date her?
I'll make an exception and support you.
I won't expose you
as a perverted gym clothes thief, either.
Wait... Really?
Sure.
That is, if Saeki doesn't know already.
She... she doesn't.
I'm sure she hasn't figured it out.
Surely, she hasn't.
She doesn't know. She doesn't know.
I'm sure she doesn't!
Kasuga, I'm sorry.
I just...
I can't stand things like this.
Does she... know?
TO BE CONTINUED
ON THE NEXT EPISODE
Kasuga is on cloud nine,
as Saeki has accepted his feelings.
But as Kasuga continues to pile up lies,
he ultimately begins to seek punishment.
Next, on episode three,
another flower of sin blooms at night
under the full moon.
Translated by Yuka Kristi